[
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Savings enable investment in _______.",
      "Answer": "innovation"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Economic prosperity is built on the foundation of _______ and savings.",
      "Answer": "production"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "High savings rates help create a _______ against economic uncertainty.",
      "Answer": "safety net"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Japanâ€™s economic resilience after disasters is attributed to its _______ culture.",
      "Answer": "savings"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "The _______ boom of the 1950s was driven by high savings rates in the U.S.",
      "Answer": "post-WWII"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Collaboration between _______ allows for greater economic outcomes.",
      "Answer": "industries"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Excessive borrowing and lack of savings lead to _______ crises.",
      "Answer": "financial"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "_______ policies often lead to unsustainable debt and economic instability.",
      "Answer": "Consumption-based"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "The foundation of long-term economic growth is _______ over immediate spending.",
      "Answer": "production"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Countries like Germany prioritize _______ to maintain sustained growth.",
      "Answer": "manufacturing"
    }
  ]
  